[
	{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "The first Pokemon ever created.",
		"answer": "Rhydon"
	},
		{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "This Pokemon almost appeared in the first Smash Bros.",
		"answer": "Meowth"
	},
		{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "What Pokemon was almost the mascot for the series?",
		"answer": "Clefairy"
	},
		{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "This Pokemon has 4 arms",
		"answer": "Machamp"
	},
		{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "This Pokemon is one of the lightest in existence.",
		"answer": "Ghastly"
	},
		{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "It is theorized that this Pokemon is the shadow of a Clefable",
		"answer": "Gengar"
	},
		{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "_______ is the longest Pokemon that can hatch from an Egg.",
		"answer": "Onyx"
	},
		{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "This pokemon is based on a living poke ball",
		"answer": "Electrode"
	},
		{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "This Pokemon has the longest tongue",
		"answer": "Lickitung"
	},
		{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "This Pokemon has no male counterpart.",
		"answer": "Chancey"
	},
		{
		"id": "11",
		"question": "This Pokemon is a genderless species",
		"answer": "Starmie"
	},
		{
		"id": "12",
		"question": "This pokemon is based on a bulky human woman",
		"answer": "Jynx"
	},
		{
		"id": "13",
		"question": "This pokemon is based on a zodiac",
		"answer": "Taurus"
	},
		{
		"id": "14",
		"question": "This pokemon only knows the attack Splash.",
		"answer": "Magikarp"
	},
		{
		"id": "15",
		"question": "An experimental Pokemon cloned from Mew's cells.",
		"answer": "Ditto"
	},
		{
		"id": "16",
		"question": "__________ has the most evolutions.",
		"answer": "Evee"
	},
		{
		"id": "17",
		"question": "This Pokemon likes to sleep alot and is known to block roads.",
		"answer": "Snorlax"
	},
		{
		"id": "18",
		"question": "This Pokemon was genetically engineered.",
		"answer": "Mewtwo"
	},
		{
		"id": "19",
		"question": "This Pokemon is the mascot of the show.",
		"answer": "Pikachu"
	},
		{
		"id": "20",
		"question": "This Pokemon puts other people and Pokemon to sleep with its voice.",
		"answer": "Jigglypuff"
	},
		{
		"id": "21",
		"question": "This Pokemon does not have eyes.",
		"answer": "Zubat"
	},
		{
		"id": "22",
		"question": "This Pokemon is known for getting powerful psychic headaches.",
		"answer": "Psyduck"
	},
		{
		"id": "23",
		"question": "This is a puppy Pokemon",
		"answer": "Growlithe"
	},
		{
		"id": "24",
		"question": "This Pokemon has a mustache",
		"answer": "Alakazam"
	},
		{
		"id": "25",
		"question": "This Pokemon is green and hates the color red.",
		"answer": "Scyther"
	}
]